indiastudychannel.com 2009-01-22

# IndiaStudyChannel privacy policy

**My Profile**

  * Sign In
  * Register
  * AdSense Revenue

**Active Members**   
_**Today**_

  * Seemark (813)
  * RK (430)
  * eldho (305)

 _ **Last 7 Days**_

  * Seemark (2584)
  * Mahesh (2013)
  * RK (1824)

more...

**Awards & Gifts**

**Online Exams**   

  * Aptitude Questions
  * General Aptitude Tests
  * Medical Entrance
  * Engineering Entrance
  * Bank Tests
  * TOEFL & IELTS Questions

Our fresher job section is exclusively for fresh graduates! Find jobs for freshers in major Indian cities including Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad, Pune or Kochi    
Find educational articles, blogs, discussion threads and other resources.    
Find details about any college in India or search for courses.

| 

At IndiaStudyChannel.com, we know that you care how information about you is stored, used and shared. We do our best to keep your trust by using the information about you carefully and sensibly. This privacy notice explains our privacy policy. By visiting IndiaStudyChannel.com, you are accepting this privacy policy and our terms & conditions.

 **How do we use the information we gather?**

IndiaStudyChannel.com is a free community site and we publish almost all information we gather in this site. **We do not share or sell your personal information to any third parties** . But all personal information you submit as part of your public profile will be publicly accessible in our site, except the email address. We try not to publish your email address to avoid spam, but it is possible that in certain cases your email address may be exposed to public.

 **What kind of information we gather?**

We store any information you submit to our site. This includes, but not limited to, the profile you create at the time of registration, the resume you post in the job section etc. If you prefer not to publish any information, you may not submit it in the site. By doing so, you may be restricted from taking advantage of certain features of the site.

 **General visitor information**

For statistical purposes, we gather and store general visitor information like Ip Address, browser version, visting time, duration etc. We may share such information with third parties or publish in our site for marketing purposes.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information stored in your computer. When you login to IndiaStudyChannel.com, we store small cookies in your computer, to provide a better browsing experience for you.

 **Advertisements**

We use advertisements from third party companies. We try to avoid any kind of offensive and harmfull advertisements in our site, but in many cases we do not have complete control of which advertisements appear in our site, due to the fact that many advertisements are automatically served by third party advertisers. We will not be responsible for any harms caused by such third party advertisements served in our site. However, if such issues are pointed to our notice, we will make all attempts to stop publishing such advertisements in our site.

 **Business Transfers**

As we continue to develop and grow our web site, we may sell IndiaStudyChannel.com or part of it. In such transactions, member information generally is one of the transferred business assets. 

|    
**Watch TV Channels**
